db.dropDatabase();

var seedQuiz1 =
{
    "Quizname": "Melbourne",
    "QnA": [
      {
        "Question": "Name this Melbourne's oldest hotel and pub on the corner of Flinders and Russell Streets built in 1850.",
        "Answer": "the DUKE hotel",
        "Lat": "-37.816388",
        "Lng": "144.969999",
        "Points": "20"
      },
      {
        "Question": "This Beyonce-inspired 68-storey skyscraper will be built in Melbourne city at this address",
        "Answer": "134 SPENCER street",
        "Lat": "-37.817278",
        "Lng": "144.953863",
        "Points": "20"
      },
      {
        "Question": "This coastal township in Melbourne harvests about 60 per cent of Australia's mussels.",
        "Answer": "PORTARLINGTON",
        "Lat": "-38.114600",
        "Lng": "144.653049",
        "Points": "10"
      },
      {
        "Question": "This bluestone-cobbled lane in the city has graffiti covered walls with sophisticated urban art.",
        "Answer": "HOSIER lane",
        "Lat": "-37.816431",
        "Lng": "144.969123",
        "Points": "10"
      },
      {
        "Question": "Off Flinders Lane, a block and a half from Swanston Street, the video clip to 'Long Way to the Top' was filmed. Name this lane.",
        "Answer": "ACDC lane",
        "Lat": "-37.815540",
        "Lng": "144.970895",
        "Points": "10"
      },
      {
        "Question": "The Melburnian idiom 'I'll meet you under the clocks' refers to the row of clocks at the entrance of what ...?",
        "Answer": "FLINDERS street station",
        "Lat": "-37.817780",
        "Lng": "144.966944",
        "Points": "10"
      },
      {
        "Question": "This historic world's oldest amusement park under management is more than 100 years old is located at...",
        "Answer": "st KILDA",
        "Lat": "-37.867713",
        "Lng": "144.976899",
        "Points": "5"
      },
      {
        "Question": "Australian-born Singer Kylie Minogue was raised in this Melbourne suburb",
        "Answer": "SURREY hills",
        "Lat": "-37.826173",
        "Lng": "145.099895",
        "Points": "5"
      },
      {
        "Question": "Vegemite was not only invented in Melbourne but every jar of Vegemite 'ever made' has come from the Melbourne factory at _ _ _ _ _ _ _ _ _'s bend ?",
        "Answer": "FISHERMAN's bend",
        "Lat": "-37.826553",
        "Lng": "144.911617",
        "Points": "5"
      },
      {
        "Question": "This vegetables, fruits, food and non-food destination in the city was once a cemetry and has roughly 9,000 people buried under its sheds and car park.",
        "Answer": "queen VICTORIA market",
        "Lat": "-37.807614",
        "Lng": "144.956806",
        "Points": "5"
      }
    ]

  };

var seedQuiz2 =
{
    "Quizname": "Landmarks1",
    "QnA": [
      {
        "Question": "Based on a fairy tale by Hans Christian Andersen, this sculpture is on a rock by the waterside in Copenhagen, Denmark.",
        "Answer": "the little MERMAID",
        "Lat": "55.692860",
        "Lng": "12.599304",
        "Points": "20"
      },
      {
        "Question": "Name this temple complex in Cambodia, the largest religious monument in the world, with site measuring 162.6 hectares.",
        "Answer": "ANGKOR wat",
        "Lat": "13.412459",
        "Lng": "103.867007",
        "Points": "20"
      },
      {
        "Question": "On the coast of Dubai, this completed artificial island takes the form of a tree, topped by a crescent.",
        "Answer": "PALM jumeirah",
        "Lat": "25.113031",
        "Lng": "55.139036",
        "Points": "10"
      },
      {
        "Question": "Name this prehistoric monument located in Wiltshire, England, the remains of a ring of standing stones set within earthworks.",
        "Answer": "STONEHENGE",
        "Lat": "51.178855",
        "Lng": "-1.826204",
        "Points": "10"
      },
      {
        "Question": "98 ft tall on a 26 ft pedestal, 92 ft wide. Name this Art Deco statue in Rio de Janeiro, Brazil.",
        "Answer": "christ the REDEEMER",
        "Lat": "-22.951946",
        "Lng": "-43.210455",
        "Points": "10"
      },
      {
        "Question": "Name this main building of the rebuilt World Trade Center complex in New York City, also the tallest skyscraper in USA.",
        "Answer": "one WORLD trade center",
        "Lat": "40.712951",
        "Lng": "-74.013030",
        "Points": "10"
      },
      {
        "Question": "Name this  Italian Renaissance church in Vatican City, the papal enclave within the city of Rome. st PETER's basillica.",
        "Answer": "st PETER's basillica",
        "Lat": "41.902167",
        "Lng": "12.453969",
        "Points": "5"
      },
      {
        "Question": "One of the 20th century's most distinctive buildings, name this multi-venue performing arts centre in Sydney, Australia.",
        "Answer": "sydney OPERA house",
        "Lat": "-33.856934",
        "Lng": "151.215270",
        "Points": "5"
      },
      {
        "Question": "Name this limestone statue of a mythical creature with a lion's body and a human head on the bank of the Nile in Giza, Egypt.",
        "Answer": "the great SPHINX",
        "Lat": "29.975232",
        "Lng": "31.137567",
        "Points": "5"
      },
      {
        "Question": "Name this white marble mausoleum and tomb located on the southern bank of the Yamuna River in the Indian city of Agra.",
        "Answer": "TAJ mahal",
        "Lat": "27.174996",
        "Lng": "78.042155",
        "Points": "5"
      }
    ]

  };


var seedQuiz3 =
{
    "Quizname": "7NewWonders",
    "QnA": [
      {
        "Question": "This pre-Columbian city at the mouth of the well of the Itza was built by the Maya people of the Terminal Classic period.",
        "Answer": "CHICHEN itza",
        "Lat": "20.684285",
        "Lng": "-88.567761",
        "Points": "20"
      },
      {
        "Question": "Often mistakenly referred to as the 'Lost City of the Incas', this 15th-century Inca site located 7,970 ft above sea level.",
        "Answer": "MACHU picchu",
        "Lat": "-13.163162",
        "Lng": "-72.544974",
        "Points": "20"
      },
      {
        "Question": "This is a historical and archaeological city that is famous for its rock-cut architecture and water conduit system.",
        "Answer": "PETRA",
        "Lat": "31.960082",
        "Lng": "35.916028",
        "Points": "20"
      },
      {
        "Question": "This is an oval amphitheatre built of concrete and sand, and is the largest amphitheatre ever built.",
        "Answer": "COLOSSEUM",
        "Lat": "41.890186",
        "Lng": "12.492231",
        "Points": "20"
      },
      {
        "Question": "98 ft tall on a 26 ft pedestal, 92 ft wide. Name this Art Deco statue in Rio de Janeiro, Brazil.",
        "Answer": "christ the REDEEMER",
        "Lat": "-22.951946",
        "Lng": "-43.210455",
        "Points": "10"
      },
      {
        "Question": "Name this wonder, a series of fortifications made of stone, brick, etc, built along an east-to-west line across northern borders of China.",
        "Answer": "great WALL of china",
        "Lat": "40.431891",
        "Lng": "116.570364",
        "Points": "5"
      },
      {
        "Question": "Name this white marble mausoleum and tomb located on the southern bank of the Yamuna River in the Indian city of Agra.",
        "Answer": "TAJ mahal",
        "Lat": "27.174996",
        "Lng": "78.042155",
        "Points": "5"
      }
    ]

  };



db.quizzes.save(seedQuiz1);
db.quizzes.save(seedQuiz2);
db.quizzes.save(seedQuiz3);

